Curriculum Vitae

Table of Contents:

>> Table of contents

>> Contact information

>> Profile

>> Skills
>> Education

>> Work experience

>> Languages

Contact information:

Name: Beau Jean van Bemmel

Title: Web developer
Nationality: Dutch
Birthdate: May 9th, 2003

Personal e-mail: <u>beauvanbemmel@live.nl</u>
School e-mail: <u>97085143@st.deltion.nl</u>

Mobile: (+31) 0636295096

Profile:

My name is Beau Jean van Bemmel and I am a software development student at Deltion College in Zwolle. I mostly focus on back-end web development using PHP and making CLI applications using Go. Perfectionistic but flexibel, experienced with SCRUM and a quick learner.

Skills:



Education:

• Software Developer

Deltion College [08/2021 - Present]

MBO 4

Curriculum:

- HTML & CSS
- Javascript
- PHP
- MySQL
- Linux
- Security

• Dienstverlening & Zorg

Landstede MBO [08/2020 - 07/2021]

MBO 1

Curriculum:

- Dutch
- Math
- Civics

Work experience:

• IT Assistant / Janitor [internship]

Landstede MBO [12/2020 - 07/2021]

Activities:

- Assisting teachers & students with IT-related problems
- Installing new computers within our network
- Cleaning & maintaining hallways & classrooms
- Enforcing rules

• QA Assistant [internship]

ICT-Kringloop Zwolle [08/2020 - 12/2020]

Activities:

- Testing secondhand keyboards, mice, monitors, speakers
- Cleaning secondhand keyboards, mice, monitors, PSUs

Languages:

	Reading	Writing	Speaking
Dutch	Native	Native	Native
English	Advanced	Advanced	Intermediate
Japanese	Beginner	Beginner	Beginner